一旦你成功安装了Android Studio
Once you install Android Studio, you can open it and
打开Android Studio并且在你进行下一步之前请检查更新  然后我们就可以开始设置Android Studio了
check for updates before proceeding. Then we can configure Android Studio.
打开Android SDK Manager查看我们已经安装了什么工具  平台版本和组件
Open up the Android SDK Manager to see what tools, platform versions, and
截止到本次录制视频的时候
components we have installed. At the time of this recording,
Android L平台已经可用  但它仍然是开发者预览模式
the Android L platform is available but it's still in developer preview mode.
这意味着它需要一直更改直到正式版发布  您不能将此应用上传到
That means it's subject to change until the official release. You can't upload
Google Play Store如果它是为Android L平台设计的
your app to Google Play if it's targeting this L platform version.
所以  我们需要使用最新的稳定版本  即Android KITKAT或者是API level 19
Hence, we want to use the latest stable platform version which is KITKAT or
API level20是为Android Wear或手表而是用的  而不是为手机和平板电脑所使用的
API level 19. API level 20 is for Android ware or watches and not for
取消选择其他所有的包  只选择API level 19的包
phones or tablets. Deselect all the other packages. And just choose the ones for
我们需要给模拟器提供SDK以及系统镜像
API level 19. We want the SDK as well as the system images for the emulator.
我们同样希望Android支持库是向后兼容的
We also want the Android Support Library for backwards compatibility. For
对于最新的版本你需要安装的所有的软件包
the most up-to-date version of all the packages you need to install,
请检查下面的链接  否则  请继续安装软件包
check the link below. Otherwise, continue with installing the packages.
选择接受许可然后选择安装  然后我们可以点击创建一个新项目
Accept the license and then install. Then we can click and
在项目向导中  我们把应用程序的名称设置为Sunshine
create a new project. In the Project Wizard, we set the app name to be Sunshine.
然后我们提供对应的包名称  为了用于分配
Then we provide a corresponding package name. For distribution purposes,
包名称应该是在Android上安装使用的全局统一的名称
the package name should be globally unique across packages installed on Android.
为了避免冲突  你可以反向使用你自己的域名地址
To avoid conflicts, you can use the reverse of the internet domain that you own.
这与Java包的命名规则是一致的  请注意
This follows the Java package naming conventions. Note that we're also using
我们为我们的Sunshine应用也使用了com.的示例命名
the com dot example namespace for our Sunshine app since it's a sample, but
因为Sunshine应用是一个样本  所以你不能使用这个名字发布到GooglePlay上
you cannot publish an app on Google play that uses this namespace.
通常情况下保持默认的建议的包名称是没有问题的  然而
Usually leaving the default package name that's suggested is fine. However,
这个类原本被老版本的Android Studio记录下来
this class was originally filmed with an older version of Android Studio which
并在包名称的末尾添加应用程序模块
added the app module at the end of the package name. So go ahead and
在本课程中如果你想让你的代码会匹配其余的代码现在就需要做出改变
make this change now if you want your code to match the rest of the code in
然后我们确认项目的位置
the course. Then we do the project location and
选择下一步  现在  我们需要选择我们的最低SDK版本
we hit next. Now, we need to choose our minimum SDK version.
在Android Studio的之前的版本中  你必须选择目标的应用的SDK
In previous versions of Android Studio, you would also have to
但是现在的项目向导会自动将目标SDK设置为最新的版本
select the target SDK. But now the Project Wizard automatically sends the target
尽管目标SDK已经为你选择好了
SDK to be the latest version. Even though target SDK is already selected for
但是重要的是要知道最低SDK和目标SDK的区别
you, it's important to know the distinction between min and target SDK